globaltexnet.com 2019-05-02

# Global Textiles —— Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

  * >  Collection of Information
  * >  Use of Information
  * >  Individual Responsibility in Regards to Privacy Protection
  * >  Disclaimers
  * >  How to Contact Us
  * >  Language

Collection of Information

Account Data: We collect all the information in your account on Globaltextiles.com, such as your company name, address, contact person, telephone number, fax number, email and etc. This is to enforce the agreement between you and Globaltextiles.com, to ensure that you are reachable by potential trade partners, or to troubleshoot problems with your account.

Hidden Data: In addition to your account data, we also collect information recorded when you browse and visit our website, including but not limited to, cookies, IP address, etc. **This information is not used to identify you, but for the necessary purpose to avoid being attacked by hackers, and for the purpose of making customized content service to users.** Additionally, through processing comprehensive statistical analysis, we are endeavoring to provide you with more and more efficient functionalities to facilitate our service. To visit Globaltextiles.com, your browser has to be configured to accept cookies.

Other Information: Sometimes we may contract with third parties to offer you products or services which we ourselves do not offer. To fully access and use such services, you may be asked to provide certain information.

Use of Information

Information, such as company name, address, contact person, telephone number, etc., will be posted on Globaltextiles.com publicly, and accessible to all users. **Users should thus exercise caution when deciding to release any information that is identifiable to you.** Globaltextiles.com conducts analysis and research on the above information regarding users' distribution of industry, geographic location, and so on. The purpose of this research is to gain a better understanding of our users, and is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Globaltextiles.com maintains the right to share analytic results with its business partners.

Individual Responsibility in Regards to Privacy Protection

Once receiving your information, we make our best effort to ensure the stability and security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure from hacker attacks. Therefore, Globaltextiles.com cannot make any warranty on the security of the information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We will disclose your information in good faith when we believe that it is necessary to:

1\. enforce the provisions of Globaltextiles.com;

2\. protect and defend the rights of Globaltextiles.com, other users, or for public interests;

3\. contract with third party parties to provide you with better value and service;

4\. conform to national regulations or legal processes.

**You as a user are strongly recommended to keep your Member ID and password on Globaltextiles.com safe and secure.** To ensure the safety and security of your company and personal information do not divulge your password to others. If you feel that your Member ID or password is for any reason at risk, please contact us immediately.

Disclaimers

We are not responsible for the privacy protection methods of other websites who are linked to Globaltextiles.com.

How to Contact Us

If you have any requests, questions or concerns about our use of your personal information and this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://img.globaltextiles.com/static/prj/inter/html/about/contact-us.html).

Language

If there is any conflict between the English version and another language version of this Privacy Policy, the English version shall prevail.

| 

### Contact us

Email:support@globaltextiles.com

Tel:+86-575-89976178

Fax:+86-575-89976100

---|---
